AMA NELSON

Freetown-western area Sierra Leone, West Africa

Tel: +23277401478/+23234063445; E-mail amanelson452@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am an experienced, mature, and caring graduate in procurement and logistics with a firm commitment to verifying and analyzing data. My experience is rooted in a solid background of working with strategic information in different circumstances, including procurement, logistics, and sales, and I am adaptable in any situation. I found myself comfortable in both solitary and group situations and have excellent communication skills, which are useful in terms of working operations.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

2023 to Date - BSc in Information System at **IPAM** (DEGREE)

2020-2022 - Emibex College of Finance and Management

Diploma in Procurement and Logistics

2005-2011 - Annie Walsh Memorial Secondary School (WASSCE)

WORKING	EXPERIENCE

2016-2017 Advocate

Pampana Communication Campbell Street Freetown

2021-2022 Saleswoman

Africell Sierra Leone Limited

2022-2023 Sales Manager

Rhapsdy Infotech Rawdon Street

INTERESTS

SKILLS: Team spirit and can work within task deadlines.

INTEREST: Reading, cooking, and singing

REFEREES:

Name: Mr. Austin lyoah

Occupation: Manager at Rhapsody Infotech Rawdon Street

Phone number: +23231976575

Name: Mr. Musa James

Occupation: Superintendent Sierra Leone Police Force

Phone number: +23288432839

Name: Miss. Aminata Fofanah

Occupation: Manager Techbrain

Phone number: +23234975454